威尔 · 森特斯: 我们开始吧，杰森，一号线,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's get going,
Jason, line one,
我们在我们的全球记忆中存储了什么？
what are we saving in our
global memory [SOUND]?
说话人2: 我们将标签用户创建器绑定到函数,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We are binding the label
user creator, to the function,
对于功能时间，威尔 · 森特斯: 太棒了。
to the function time
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic.
就是这个。
There it is.
有一个函数定义。
There's a function definition.
下一行，到伊森，一直往下，打左手边的什么,
Next line, over to Ethan, all the way
down, to hit, what, on the left-hand side,
演讲者2: 定义一个常量用户1。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Defining a const user one.
威尔 · 森特斯: 顺便说一句，我想告诉你们,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: By the way,
I want to tell you people,
只要知道你有多不寻常，即使是在专业的工程环境中
just know how unusual you are, even in
the professional engineering environment
你现在只要去，是的，酷，JavaScript 线程去那里。
that you now just go, yeah, cool,
JavaScript thread goes away down there.
就像那是非标准的，即使是完全的，如此直观的再生,
Like that is non standard, to even have
that fully, so intuitive regrowth,
你刚才的表现 Ethan 太棒了。
what you did there, Ethan, excellent.
现在。
Now.
天啊，我睡得太香了。
My God, I just slept terribly.
哇！
Wow!
我累了。
I'm getting tired.
我为什么要这么做？
Why did I just do that?
对不起，各位。
Sorry, everybody.
你知道一号用户要输入什么吗？
Do you have any idea what's
gonna go in user one?
不知道。
No idea.
我这样做几乎是好的，因为这就像，我们不知道。
It's almost good that I did that,
cuz it's like, we have no idea.
因为我们要离开去做什么，伊森？
Because we've gotta go off and
do, what, Ethan?
演讲者2: 一个呼叫用户创建器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A call user creator.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，与此同时,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Right,
and in the meantime,
一号用户肯定不是一个物体，也不知道它会是什么,
user one is definitely not an object,
and it has no idea what it's gonna be,
事实上是这样吗？
it's in fact instead?
说话人2: 未初始化。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Uninitialized.
威尔 · 森特斯: 没有初始化，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Uninitialized, exactly.
谢谢你，彼得，你也会这么说，伊森，所以
Thank you Peter, you're gonna say
the same thing, that, as well, Ethan, so
我们打电话给用户创造者。
let's call user creator.
我们已经进入决赛了，各位。
We're in the final straight here, people.
最后，最后，最后一个回路，最后一个直道。
Well, the final, the final, the final
loop, the final straight of the final.
好吧，我不知道。
All right, I don't know.
我本该继续前进的，好吧，我们正在失去它。
I was meant to be moving on,
alright, we're losing it.
所以，我们开始了，我们称之为用户创造者,
So, there we go,
we're calling user Creator,
全新的-演讲者2: 执行环境。
brand new-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution context.
执行上下文，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
spot on, exactly.
我们开始吧。
Into it we go.
你们每个人都很紧张。
Very intense at all of you.
我们开始吧。
Into it we go.
好了，开始了。
Okay, here we go.
在本地记忆里，让我们,
And in the Local Memory, let's have,
让我们请出我们的朋友 Dan。
let's have our friend, Dan.
Dan，让我们来处理第一件事，我们总是在执行函数时处理
Dan, let's handle the first thing, we
always handle when we execute a function
调用一个函数，那就是处理我们的？
call a function, and
that is to handle our?
讲者二: 论点。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Arguments.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们的论点，都是人类的第一个论点，是意志，是人类的第一个论点
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Our arguments, and
are all human first one is will, and
它的参数是什么？
its parameter which is assigned is?
讲者2: 姓名 威尔 · 森特斯: 名字，是的,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Name.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Name, yeah,
准确地说，是因为它被冻住了，各位。
let's be really precise,
it was because it's bit froze, people.
我上周给了你这个，你知道那个小工程师，他们
I gave this to you last week,
you know the small engineer, they were
被我们将要看到的东西抛出一点，因为我可以看到两个名字，在下面的那行。
thrown a bit by what we're at to see, cuz
I can see two names, in that line below.
我们马上就知道为什么了。
We'll see why, in a second.
好的，名字，很好。
Okay, name, excellent.
下一个参数是？
And then the next parameter is?
演讲者2: 得分，三分。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Score, value of three.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah.
难道没有人认为这些是属性吗。
Don't anybody think that
these are properties.
这些只是数据变量，你知道，标签，就像其他的一样。
These are just data variables,
you know, labels, like any other.
它们只是一些，我们必须为它们留下一个占位符，在早期，和
They're just ones, which we got to
leave a placeholder for, early on, and
然后在运行函数时预填充。
then prefilled when we run the function,
okay.
现在，我们进入函数体。
Now, we enter the body of the function.
布莱登，一号线怎么办？
Braden, what do we do in line one?
Speaker 2: 声明常量 new user，这是一个新对象。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Declare constant new user,
which is a new object.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 太棒了，谢谢你，布莱登。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
thank you, Braden.
好了轮到你了 Kayla。
Okay, over to you, Kayla.
等一下，我总是很纠结这个问题。
Hold on [LAUGH],
I always really struggle with that.
轮到你了 Kayla。
Over to you, Kayla.
扬声器3: 我们正在为新用户设置属性名
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We are setting
the property name on the new user
反对-威尔 · 桑坦斯: 我喜欢这个。
object-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I love that.
Speaker 3: 参数名的值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: To the value
of the argument name.
威尔 · 森特斯: 太好了，说得太对了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's excellent,
that's spot-on.
这一点非常重要，因为它确实有点重要
Now, that's really important there,
because it is a bit
奇怪的是，我们说，去寻找新用户，并有种暗示，有
odd that we are saying, go look for
new user, and kind of implying that there
是一个名称属性，或者如果对象中没有创建它。
is a name property on it, or if there
isn't create it now within the object.
这不是一个变量，对吗？
This is not a variable, right?
这不是标签，这不是标识符。
This is not a label,
this is not an identifier.
这是对象上的属性，新用户。
This is a property on the object,
new user.
正如 Kayla 所说创建它然后分配给它任何东西,
Exactly as Kayla said, create it,
and assign to it whatever,
进入等号的右边，右边的那个,
so into the right-hand side of the equals,
whatever is on the right hand-side there,
去回忆一下吧。
go look for that in memory.
它将添加字符串 will，并且我们正确地存储在名称中。
It will add the string will, and
we stored in the name properly.
正如凯拉所说。
Exactly as Kayla said.
我们再来一遍 Kayla 如果你不介意下一句台词是什么？
Let's do it again, Kayla, if you mind,
what's the next line say to do?
扬声器3: 我们将新用户对象的属性值设置为 score,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We set the property score on
the new user object to the value of score,
也就是2。
which is 2.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我们的论点，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
our argument, exactly.
参数 score 是存储在那里的参数值3。
The parameter score is what
the argument value, 3, stored in there.
丹，这是最后一块了，我们要做什么？
Dan, final piece here, what are we doing?
演讲者2: 我们正在创造一个增量
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We are creating a increment
威尔 · 斯坦斯: 是的。
function-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yep.
说话人2: 关于新用户-威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: On new user-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, exactly.
说到这里，威尔 · 森塔斯: 就是这里,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: And saying that-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it is,
保存所有代码，保存所有代码，考虑保存所有代码。
saving all its code, saving all its code,
think about saving all its code.
但是我想要那样，因为我想要能够在一秒钟之内做出新的用户。
But I want that, because I wanna be able
to do new user, well, within a second.
在那里，我有一个美丽的对象。
There it is, I've a beautiful object.
这里有我需要的一切。
It's got everything I need.
但是，Jeff，它被限制在用户创建器的执行上下文中。
But, Jeff, it's stuck inside
the execution context of user creator.
我需要做什么才能把它输出到用户1中？
What do I need to do to get it out,
into user one?
我退回去，完全正确，退回去。
I return it, exactly right, return it out.
要知道这里的整个部分实际上是求值的,
And know that this whole portion
here actually evaluates,
转换成这个返回对象，并存储这个不寻常的。
turns into this return that object,
and store that unusual.
就这样，就这样,
So there we go, there it is,
用户一个对象，看看这个，人们,
the user one object, and
look at that, people,
和我们之前设置的一模一样。
it's exactly the same
as our previous set up.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 就是这样，现在我们有了我们美丽的功能。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it is, and
now we have our beautiful function there.
我想说一件小事，我不想死。
I want to say one little thing,
that I don't, die.
我们来看第二部分。
We'll come to the second.
让我们回到现在的 global，点击下一行，声明用户2。
Let's go back to global as we are, and
hit our next line, declaring user 2.
我要在这里做这个，尽管看起来有点重复，因为我希望你这么做
I'm gonna do this one here, even though
it seems repetitive, cuz I want you to
找出一些可能有点多余的，或者非常多余的，或者。
spot something that may be a little
bit redundant, or very redundant, or.
从根本上来说，从字面上来说,
Fundamentally, and word fundamentally,
而且，不要介意，基本上是多余的。
and, nevermind, fundamentally redundant.
我们要再运行一次用户创建器，我们要创建
We're gonna run user creator one
more time, we're gonna create
一个新的执行环境，这个汤米保尔森，蒂姆，和五。
a new execution context,
this Tommy Paulson, Tim, and five.
我的朋友是我的同学。
My friend is my friend from, from school.
非常好的朋友。
Very good friends.
我不知道为什么，我早就应该改掉这些名字了。
I don't know why, I should have
changed these names long ago.
我认为我想在 OP 版本的所有，但是
I thought I think in
the OP version of all, but
我确实改了名字，我不知道为什么很久以前，四年前,
I did change the names, I do not
know why long ago, four years ago,
我把它称为蒂姆，我的朋友，我研究生院唯一的朋友。
I put it as Tim, my friend,
my only friend from grad school.
事实上，我想把它记录下来，我有很多，不,
Actually, I wanna get it on the record,
I have many, no,
不，即使是他，我也不确定他把我当朋友。
no, [LAUGH] even him,
I'm not sure he considers me a friend.
好吧，不管怎样，我想他把我当成同事了。
All right, anyway,
I think he considers me a colleague.
好的，在这个执行上下文中，我们会这样做，Will Sentance: i’ ll
Okay, so in this execution context we go
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I'll
暂时先小点声。
keep it small, for now.
在当地的记忆里，威尔 · 森特斯: 我们将会有,
And in the local memory,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We're gonna have,
我不知道为什么我把它弄得这么小，但是我们开始吧。
I don't know why I made it this small,
but here we go.
名字，蒂姆，得分，5分。
Name, Tim, score, five.
然后我们创建一个对象，新用户。
We then create an object, new user.
这真的很糟糕，我不知道为什么我把它做得这么小。
This is really bad,
I don't know why I made this so small.
一个对象，具有名称属性的新用户,
An object, new user with a name property,
保存到 name 参数的值，该参数的参数为2。
save that to the value of the name
parameter, whose argument was two.
得分，五，为什么我把它弄得这么小？
Score, five, why did I make it so small?
我不知道。
I do not know.
并且，增量，保存一个品牌
And, increment, save a brand
新的函数，所有的代码。
new function, all of its code.
所以我知道对于这个对象，当它返回到用户2时,
So I know that on that object,
when it gets returned out into user two,
它将会有一个美丽的,
it's gonna have a beautiful,
它会有一个漂亮的增量方法。
it's gonna have a beautiful
increment method on it.
名字，蒂姆，分数,
There it is, name, Tim, score,
5和递增是一个函数,
five, and increment, is a function,
现在我们要做最重要的检查。
and now we do our all important check.
我们可以做，用户2，点，或者其中任何一个，但是
Can we do, user 2, dot,
or any of them, but
这就是 user2.increment。
that's the user2.increment.
托德，在你，查找时间，用户2，它在哪里？
Todd, over to you, look up time,
user 2, where is it?
演讲者2: 在全局记忆中。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In global memory.
威尔 · 森特斯: 全局记忆，我们拥有它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Global memory,
we have it.
讲者2: 是的 威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, it is.
增量，它是一个属性，它是用户2上的一个方法吗？
Increment, is it a property,
is it a method on user 2?
讲者2: 是的 威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，我们抓住了它。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, it is, we grab it.
我现在不打算执行。
I'm not gonna execute it right now.
但是想想增量代码是怎么说的。
But just think about what
increments code says.
它说，新用户点评 + + ，但我很确定这里没有新用户。
It says, new user dot score++, but I'm
pretty sure there's no new user out here.
而我们失去了这一点。
And we lost that.
除非存储在这里的函数增量有一个[ CROSSTALK ]背包,
Unless the function increment that was
stored in here had a [CROSSTALK] backpack,
这是一个链接的名称，旧的名称为同一个函数，意味着如果我运行,
which was a link to the name, the old name
for the same function, meaning if I run,
作为一个小小的奖励，同志们，不要担心这个，如果你去,
as a very little brief bonus, and, people,
don't worry about this, if you go,
当我运行 increment you 时，因为我们不会使用这个样式。
when I run increment you,
because we're not going to use this style.
我们永远不会用这种风格，所以我们不需要详细讨论它。
We're never gonna use this style,
so we don't need to dwell on it.
但是请注意闭包是如何随处可见的，对象被返回,
But just notice how closure is everywhere,
the object gets returned out,
里面的增量函数是 newUser.score + + 。
the increment function inside
of it says newUser.score++.
新用户在哪里？
Where's newUser?
这个执行上下文，让我们明确一点，已经被删除了。
This execution context,
let's be clear, has been deleted.
两者都被删除了，但是，因为对象返回时已经有了
Both have been deleted, but, because
the object, when it returned out had
上面的一个函数，这个函数与周围的所有记忆相连
a function on it, that function was
linked to all the surrounding memory
包括新用户，这是同一个对象的标签。
including the new user, which was
a label for the very same object.
我的意思是，我们得到的新用户标签仍然是在 increment 中，并且
I mean we get the new user label
still inside of increment, and
它将引用 user2。
it will refer to user2.
背包到处都是。
The backpack is everywhere.
我只是想给你点奖励,
I just wanna give that a little bonus,
因为我们在这次治疗中看到了背包，不过别担心。
because we saw the backpack in this
session, but don't worry about it.
因为我们永远不会使用这种方法。
Because we're never going
to use this approach.
但是这种方法从根本上起了作用，容易理解吗？
But this approach fundamentally
has worked, easy to reason about?
当然了。
You bet it is.
我的函数就在这里，在点的右边，我可以
I've got my function right there, to the
right-hand side of my dot, I can literally
谷歌搜索预填，用户2点，它将填写。
have it Google Search pre-filled,
user two dot, it's gonna fill in.
如果我有其他功能存储在那里，他们都会在那里,
If I had other functions stored on there,
they'd all be there,
我可以开始写作，然后他们就会出现。
I could start writing, and
they're literally gonna show up.
这是你选择的抄本的设计，但它说明了一个事实
That's the design of the codex of your
choice, but it speaks to the fact
这些函数绝对是，字面上的对象。
that those functions are absolutely,
literally on the object.
可供下载。
Available.
太美了，太棒了。
Beautiful, wonderful.
说完了吗？
Are we done?
我们结束了。
We're done.
很容易理解不需要功能性的打猎,
Easy to reason about,
no hunting with functions,
没有想到这个函数实际上适用于我的测验用户。
no thinking this function
actually applies to my quiz user.
我的测验问题17，因为它在这个物体上
My quiz question 17,
because it's on this object, and
然而，这种方法是完全不可用的，因为我说
yet this approach is completely unusable,
because I said
还有另外两个目标，我的范例，我说的，是什么？
there were two other goals, and
my paradigm, what I say, they were?
很容易添加新的功能，但是,
Easy to add features to new,
new functionality, and nevertheless,
正式来说，大家告诉我，这种风格,
officially before when, people,
tell me what, with this style,
我永远不会用这个，丹，继续。
is fundamentally wrong, that I could
never use this, Dan, go ahead.
说话人2: 我们把同一个功能存储了两次。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're storing
the same function twice.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 他说得对。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He's spot on.
我们无法摆脱它，这些数据我们无法摆脱。
There's no getting away from it,
that this data we can't.
我们不能，你知道，不存储 t 和5，Will 和3，那是不同的数据。
We can't, you know, not store T and five,
Will and three, that's different data.
我再讲一个故事，它不同，但是这个函数的代码
So I got a story again, it's different,
but the code of this function, and
这个函数的代码是相同的
the code of this function,
is identical, and
如果我有500个用户需要增量函数，所以
if I've got 500 users who need to
have the increment function, so
我们可以做一个703。 我说我们五个人，然后使用495。 增量。
that we can do us a 703.increment, I say
five of us, and use it 495.increment.
我得有一份副本，对吧？
I gotta have a copy of it, right?
不管怎样，我只有一个函数，100,200,3,4,
And if either way, I just got one
function, I have 100, 200, three, four,
五个，差不多几百个。
five, literally hundreds.
他们都会被叫去吗我会把他们每个人的名字都复印一份,
Are they all gonna be called,
I'm gonna have copies of each of them,
每个都可能有10行代码。
each of them maybe 10 lines of code.
我有1000个用户，相当于10000个。
I've got 1000 users, as 10,000.
每个函数都是100。
And then each function is 100.
我在这里浪费了上千行代码中的10行。
I'm wasting 10s of thousands of lines,
of codes here.
因此，内存中的空间也会增加。
So, space in memory will also add.
还有另外一件让人头疼的事情，也许，或者
Also another thing that's a pain
in the ass about this, perhaps, or
有点问题是的 Peter。
problematic about this, yeah, Peter.
演讲者2: 如果你想增加一个功能,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you wanted
to add a feature to this,
你必须把它添加到每个用户。
you'd have to add it to each user.
威尔 · 森特斯: 完全正确，就像我说的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Perfect,
exactly as I say.
是的，完全正确，如果我们想添加函数，就必须手动添加
Yeah, spot on, we would have to add
the function manually if we wanted to add
一个功能，这是新的功能。
a feature, which is new functionality.
手动添加到每个对象中。
Manually add it to every single object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 但我要说的是，超级直觉。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But
I will say this, super intuitive.
没有什么神秘的，当然我可以使用增量函数 user2,
There is no mystery, of course I can
use the increment function user2,
就在那个物体上。
it's right there on the object.
使用函数问题生成对象，每次我们创建一个新用户,
Generate objects using a function
problems, every time we create a new user,
我们在计算机内存中留出空间，用于我们的数据功能。
we make space in that computer's memory,
for our data functions.
但是这个函数只是相同代码的拷贝。
But that function are just
copies of the same code.
还有更好的办法吗？
Is there a better way?
我们走着瞧。
We'll see.